viedu.org 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy - Visions In Education

Visions In Education is committed to protecting your privacy. This Visions In Education Privacy Statement applies to data collected by Visions In Education (Visions) website services.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  
At Visions website, we may ask you to provide personal information, such as your email address, name, home address, or telephone number on various data collection forms within our website.

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
Visions collects your personal information to help us efficiently contact you about your request for information and/or to contact you regarding your interest in our school. We may also use your personal information to send out surveys to share your experience with our school and help us to improve our services.

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**  
Except as required by law, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Visions In Education. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

**Communication Preferences**  
You can stop the delivery of future communication email from Visions by following the specific instructions in the email you receive.

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
At Visions In Education, we are committed to protecting the security of your information, including personal information, and information collected for enrollment purposes. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

**Contacting Us**  
Visions welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us at 1-833-883-1601.

**Acceptable Use Policy**

Visions In Education has policies regarding the use of school computers and access to the Internet.

You may [review our policies here](https://www.viedu.org/acceptable-use-policy/).

© 2019 Visions In Education.
